<game>
    <state type="set_background">
        <value>images/kevin_room.jpg</value>
    </state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_with_button">
        <speaker>(Scene Setup)</speaker>
        <dialogue>Hamlet is being interrogated by Detective Claudius and Officer Rosencrantz as to the whereabouts of the slain Polonius, who Hamlet killed and  hid the body.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>Hamlet, we know you killed Polonius. Where did you put the body? Polonius deserved a proper burial.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>I have hid the body somewhere safe.</choice>
        <choice>I burned the body.</choice>
        <choice>I dumped it into a lake.</choice>
    </state>

    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>

    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Officer Rosencrantz</speaker>
        <dialogue>Hamlet, stop playing games and tell us where the body is. The family is grieving and wants to put him to rest.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>He was an evil man who does not deserve a proper burial.</choice>
        <choice>I'm never going to tell you.</choice>
        <choice>I'm not going to answer any of these inquiries.</choice>
    </state>

    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Officer Rosencrantz</speaker>
        <dialogue>Everyone deserves a proper burial.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>I don't even want to listen to you. You're just a suck up, only listening to and obeying what Detective Claudius says so you can get a promotion.</choice>
        <choice>Okay, he's hidden in the top of the North tower.</choice>
        <choice>I forgot where he is.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Officer Rosencrantz</speaker>
        <dialogue>Wait a second. Are you insulting me?!</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>Yes, you are just trying to suck up to Detective Claudius by doing whatever he asks of you! You literally soak up everything he has to say.</choice>
        <choice>No, sorry I didn't mean it.</choice>
        <choice>Maybe, maybe not. Who's to say I am?</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Officer Rosencrantz</speaker>
        <dialogue>I don't understand why you are saying this to me.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>Yeah, you probably don't. You're a fool.</choice>
        <choice>I really don't like your attitude.</choice>
        <choice>I'm telling you this for your own good.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_with_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius (to other Officers, without Hamlet hearing)</speaker>
        <dialogue><i>We are probably not going to get the location out of him, so go out and search for the body yourselves.</i></dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>Hamlet, this is the final time we are going to ask you. <b>WHERE DID YOU PUT THE BODY?</b></dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>He's taken care of.</choice>
        <choice>I burned the body and buried it.</choice>
        <choice>I cut him into pieces and fed him to tigers.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>How is he taken care of?</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>He is where he deserves.</choice>
        <choice>I put a Bible on his chest.</choice>
        <choice>You'll have to trust me.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>He deserves a big funeral and burial in an extravagant grave!</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>Every man ends up the same way after death.</choice>
        <choice>Of course! He makes an extravagant main course for the worms!</choice>
        <choice>Perhaps that would be the more reasonable choice.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>What do you mean?</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>It's up to interpretation.</choice>
        <choice>He was fat, so he's not as deserving of a good burial.</choice>
        <choice>I don't like him.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>I promise this is the last time I will ask you before I lock you up. Where did you put the body?</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>He's in heaven. If you don't find him in heaven you should go search for him in hell. But if you don't find him in a month, you should be able to smell him somewhere within the castle.</choice>
        <choice>He's in hell. If you don't find him in hell, don't bother to keep searching. But if you don't find him in a month, you should be able to smell him.</choice>
        <choice>He is exactly where I designated his body to be.</choice>
    </state>
    
    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_no_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius (to Officers)</speaker>
        <dialogue>Go find him!</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="choice_box">
        <choice>Take your time! He's not going anywhere.</choice>
        <choice>Why the hurry? Polonius is of little importance</choice>
        <choice>Take your time! Laertes and Ophelia won't feel better rushing to bury Polonius with such formalities.</choice>
    </state>

    <state type="hide_choice_box"></state>

    <state type="dialogue_with_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius</speaker>
        <dialogue>Hamlet, I'm sending you off to England.</dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="dialogue_with_button">
        <speaker>Detective Claudius (Hamlet cannot hear)</speaker>
        <dialogue><i>Make sure he is killed the minute he steps off the plane</i></dialogue>
    </state>
    
    <state type="complete_game"></state>
</game>
